(Sheldon:)Good night, Dr. Fowler.
(Amy:)Good night, Dr. Cooper.
(Sheldon:)Good night, indeed.
(Sheldon:)What a rube.
(Sheldon:)Why would I put on lotion
when I have such soft hands?
(Bernadette:)You were really quiet during dinner.
Is everything okay?
(Howard:)Yeah. I guess I was just thinking
about my mom,
(Howard:)and how sad my childhood was.
(Bernadette:)Yeah, I bet it sucked.
(Bernadette:)I'm gonna take a bath.
You do the dishes.
(Howard:)How about I take a bath with you
and see what happens.
Here's what's gonna happen:
(Bernadette:)I'm gonna take a bath,
and you're gonna do the dishes.
(Sheldon:)That's it?
No compassion?
(Bernadette:)Aw, poor Howie.
We good? I'm gonna take a bath.
(Howard:)Bernie...
(Bernadette:)God, what is going on with you?
(Howard:)I'm sharing my pain.
(Bernadette:)And I'm not buying it. Try again.
(Howard:)I'm learning to be a man In a culture
(Howard:)where it's increasingly difficult
to know how.